ILR School CAHRS Records /4304
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School CAHRS Records
1987-2006
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
Center for Advanced Human Resource Studies
/4304
6 cubic feet
6 linear ft.
Records.
8238019
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, November 25, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 05, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4304 AV: ILR School CAHRS Audio-Visual Materials
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Center for Advanced Human Resource Studies
8238019
- CAHRS prospects, A-G (Box 1)
  - ABB News, 1993-1999 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Air Touch News, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Amgen News, 1995-1999 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - ARCO Chemical Co., 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - AT&T Global Info. Solutions, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - AT&T News, 1988-2000 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Avon Products, 1991-1999 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - BAE Systems N. America, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - BASF Aktiengesellschaft, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Baxter Health Care, 1990-2002 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Baxter International, 1998-2000 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Becton Dickinson, 1991-1995 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Bell Atlantic, 1990-1999 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Blue Cross & Blue Shield of Maryland, 1991-1995 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - British-American Tobacco Marketing (Singapore) Pte. Ltd., 1997-2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - British Airways POC, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - British Petroleum, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Charles Schwab & Co., 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Chevron Texaco, 1991-2004 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Continental Air, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Coty, 2000-2002 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - DHL International, 1994-1997 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Digital Equipment Corp., 1988-1993 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - DuPont, 1998-2004 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Eastman Kodak, 1991-2000 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Exxon Corp., 1991-2001 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - FISERV, 1993-1997 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Florida Power and Light, 1995-2005 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - General Motors, 1994-2002 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - GrupoNueva, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- CAHRS prospects, H-W (Box 2)
  - Hartford Financial, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Hallmark Cards, 1990-2000 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Hewlett-Packard, 1995-1999 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Home Depot, 2000-2003 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Ingersoll-Rand Co., 1993-2000 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - LG Group, 1995-1999 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Medtronic, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Minnesota Mining & Manufacturing Co., 1988-2000 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Mobil Oil Corp., 1990-2000 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Monsanto, 2002-2004 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Motorola, 1997-2000 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - PepsiCo Inc., 1992-2000 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Petroleos de Venezuela, 1992-2003 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Pfizer, 1991-2003 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Pharmacia Corporation, 1991-2002 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Riverwood International, 1997-2005 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - St. Paul Companies, 1998-2002 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Storage Tech, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - The Limited, 1996-2003 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Toys "R" Us, 2001-2003 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Union Carbide, 1987-1994 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Unisys Corp., 1996-1998 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Visteon Auto. Systems, 2000-2003 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Waterford-Wedgewood, 2000-2002 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Williams-Sonoma, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- CAHRS Advisory board material books, 97-02 (Box 3)
  - Advisory Board Meeting Book, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Advisory Board Meeting Book, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Advisory Board Meeting Book, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Advisory Board Meeting Book, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Advisory Board Meeting Book, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Advisory Board Meeting Book, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Advisory Board Meeting Book, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Advisory Board Meeting Book, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Advisory Board Meeting Book, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - CAHRS Advisory Board Retreat, 1995-2004 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Advisory Board, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - CAHRS Fall 2004 Advisory Board Meeting (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Spring 2004 Advisory Board Meeting April 8, 2004 -- NYC (Box 3, Folder 13)
- CAHRS sponsor meeting materials, 02-05 spring meeting Budapest (Box 4)
  - Tyco, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Spring International 2005 Budapest, 2004-2005 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Spring International 2005 Budapest, 2003-2005 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Orientation 2004 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Starbucks Coffee, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Fall 2014 Meeting, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Spring Sponsor Meeting May 2004, 2003-2004 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Berlin May 2002, 2000-2002 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Fall 2003 Sponsor Meeting Nov. 2003 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Fall 2003 Sponsor Meeting Nov. 2003 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- CAHRS sponsor meeting books, 2000- 2003 (Box 5)
  - CAHRS E-Business Strategy Success, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - CAHRS E-Business Strategy Success, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - CAHRS Executive Briefing Profiling Honeywell, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - CAHRS The Global HR Value Proposition: HR Measurement and Marketing, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - CAHRS The Global HR Value Proposition: HR Measurement and Marketing, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - CAHS Taking Internet Staffing to the Next Level: Strategic Hiring Management Systems, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - CAHRS Managing Human Capital in the European Union and Beyond, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - CAHRS Restoring Trust: HR's Role in Corporate Governance, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - CAHRS Global Leadership Study: Survey of ILR & JGSM Students and Sponsor Companies, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Spring Advisory Board Meeting, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Models of Strategic HRM: A Global Perspective, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Act Globally, Act Locally: Balancing Global and Local Needs in HR Systems, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Global Sourcing and Domestic Competitiveness: HR Issues and Responses, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- SK books 04 and 02, student spiral white books from conferences, and CAHRS expenses 03-04 (Box 6)
  - Custom Human Resource Executive Development Program, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Custom Human Resource Executive Development Program, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Central & Eastern Europe: Business & HR Implications, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - The Talent Management Challenge, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Organizational Growth & HR Implications, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Shell (Instead), 2004 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - American Express, 2003-2004 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - International Education, 1996-2002 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - International Education, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - CAHRS Sponsor Check, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - HR Paradigm, 2003-2004 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Shell, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Sanyo(PW)-OSP, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - 3606 Ithaca, 1998-2000 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Fall 2001 IHREDP, 1989-2001 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - HR Paradigm, 2003-2004 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Board Meetings, 2003-2004 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Communications, 2003-2005 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Sponsor Development, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Outside Sponsorships, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Library Searches, 2003-2004 (Box 6, Folder 21)